Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Got You!
Episode 43
Where did she run off to?
She couldn’t have gone far.
These pieces of furniture…
can actually…
move.
She’s back. What do we do now?
Come on out.
Since we’ve been discovered,
there’s no need to hide anymore.
Great, they didn’t spot me.
But I spotted you.
You bumped into me, a noble sofa.
And you nearly bumped into me, too.
There’s a big cabinet.
Let’s try hiding in there.
It’s finally our turn to make an appearance.
What on earth are these creatures?
You have nowhere left to run.
Who exactly are you people, and what do you want?
It looks like you were the one who barged in first.
If you let my friend go, we’ll leave right now.
That’s not up to us to decide. Our Young Miss gave orders
that no one is allowed to mess with things here, for any reason.
Young Miss?
Wait, she’s a girl.
Let’s not be too rough.
Then let’s wrap her up,
and wait for Young Miss to return and decide how to handle her.
That’s a good idea.
I’ll grab her.
Alright.
You guys
don’t go too far
I didn’t expect her to have backup; let’s all attack together
Watch this
I almost didn’t make it
Luckily, I’m okay now
There’s nothing wrong outside the window
Why are they so scared?
We aren’t afraid of anything; you should be the one who’s scared.
Let’s catch her together
Okay
Why haven’t Tibbie and Jonie come out yet?
Have they really been caught?
There is absolutely no way the two of them can escape Pink’s manor.
Wait, the manor you’re talking about—is it Pink’s?
But isn’t that person named Pink
off in another world, fighting Weslie and the others for the fragments?
If she isn’t there,
then what is there to be afraid of?
Then you’re underestimating her.
Stop keeping us in suspense.
Just tell us who exactly is behind all this.
When we first arrived here,
this world indicated the presence of only two fragments.
One was in the Silt Area, and the other was in the Xilan Tree’s Trial Zone.
You guys already took the fragment from the Silt Area.
To get the Xilan Tree fragment, a Flower Baby has to be brought to enter the Trial Zone.
The one holding the fragment is likely her—who managed to enter the Trial Zone,
Mei Huahua.
So, it is someone from the Flower Tribe causing trouble.
No, she isn’t necessarily from the Flower Tribe.
When Lan Baobao and I were searching for the Spark,
we encountered a mysterious person.
She kept causing accidents to injure the Flower Babies who were searching for the Spark.
There was only one goal:
To stop other Flower Babies from entering the Trial Grounds.
In other words, that mysterious person and Mei Huahua are companions?
People in Flower Tribe don’t know about the fragment.
So I guess this Mei Huahua is
disguised by the mysterious person.
Just like me pretending to be a member of the Flower Tribe.
Weslie’s analysis is great.
Acting cool again
But I didn’t understand
Why did she need to capture Lan Baobao after she got the fragment?
Although I don’t know the specific reason, it should be related to the fragment.
That means, we can just grab this Mei Huahua
and everything that happens in this world can be solved
Not only this world
Even the mastermind who attacked us in the first place can be found.
What you said makes sense
Then let’s go find her and rescue Lan Baobao.
Planie can’t go
You have a fragment on your body; she will definitely come to find you.
Don’t worry, I will protect Planie and the fragment.
Planie
That Mei Huahua moves really fast
After her!
Stop fighting, stop fighting
Stop fighting
It was you, Silt Tribe, who took action first.
It was you who hurt our queen first.
Told you we didn’t
Come again
Flower Tribe Elder
Don’t fight anymore
It’s you. Why did you let Silt Tribe attack our Flower Tribe?
It was just a misunderstanding. Someone pretended to be a flower and hurt me.
That’s why they—
Who else pretends to be a flower besides Weslie?
Elder, Mentor Mei Huahua has a question
She took the multicolored fragment from the trial zone
and even trapped me. Fortunately, I was smart enough to escape.
Everyone should be careful about her
Mei Huahua
I never thought she would do such a thing
Elder, the Xilan Tree has a big hole
The most important thing now is for us to work together to solve this problem
Elder, let’s go see it once.
Everyone, let’s go down below and see what’s going on.
Be careful
Hand over the fragment
This is the energy of our world and I will never give it to you
Then take the move
If you only have this little strength left, don’t do so many things anymore.
Are you not even going to pretend now?
Just leave it to me to finish what you can’t do.
Just you?
With the power of my hand
That problem has been solved long ago
Planie, are you okay?
My fragment was taken away by her
You want to catch me with just a piece of wool
You underestimate the power of three fragments
What’s going on
Weslie
No, it’s like she has no physical body at all
what should we do
Okay, I won’t play with you anymore.
end it
We need to deal with her quickly
Otherwise Young Miss’s secret will be discovered
How on earth am I going to force the owner of this place to come out?
And my favorite Colorful Dandelions.
dandelion?
that’s it
Bear, help me get that bouquet of flowers
Her goal is Colorful Dandelions
What is she trying to do?
No, we have to stop her.
Looks like I guessed right; this flower is the key.
Do you realize what I’m capable of now?
You’d better just surrender quietly.
I should be the one saying that to you.
This is—
What’s happening to her?
Give back the Colorful Dandelion right now!
We’re backing off—don’t do anything rash.
Hold it steady.
Make the owner of this place come out and see me.
We’re done for.
So this is the power of three fragments?
What’s happening over there?
No, I can’t waste any more time.
Give the fragments back.
You guys are such a nuisance.
She’s trying to escape.
She has the fragments; we can’t let her get away.
The fragments are right there.
Silt photosphere shot!
She’s pinned down.
Weslie, hurry!
I’ll let you off the hook this time.
That Mei Huahua is really strange.
Suddenly, she doesn’t want the fragment anymore.
Fragments…
Keep them safe.
Thank you, Weslie.
Oh no, the earthquake is starting again.
It feels like the Xilan Tree is failing.
Look, it’s Lan Baobao.
He’s okay now.
The Flower Tribe has gone down to the Silt Area.
Let’s hurry over and see if we can help.
Wait for us!
Who exactly is getting in my way?
Uh-oh, Miss Pink is angry.
We’re done for.
To be continued